<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AppBelchior</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">140553099914903</string>
    <string name="textoTelaInicial">" Your songs are graffiti on the walls. Find and listen."</string>
    <string name="btnConect">Connect</string>
    <string name="termos_de_uso_texto">By registering for the application of the Application, the User automatically submits to all rules and conditions of the Terms of Use: The Application allows the User to have access to information and contents related to publications of AppBelchior. Within this context, the User may interact with the ae with the contacts of his profile sending or publishing texts, images, images and access to other functionalities made available by the Application. A single registration per User shall be allowed, and access, display and use of the Application for the User in a personal and non-transferable person shall be permitted. The User may not, in any case, share the Application in any site or virtual environment, nor use the user register, without their respective authorization. In these cases, AppBelchior reserves the right to block access without prior notice to the User. We recommend that the user to have access 14 (fourteen) full years, at least. In the case of minors under eighteen (18) and other persons who require representation under the law, they must be duly represented or assisted, as the case may be, by their legal parents or legal, who are required to register as a representative You are looking for User, being fully responsible for this for your actions. AppBelchior reserves the right, without notice, to cancel and / or block User\'s access at any time if found to have engaged in any act or conduct that (i) violates federal, state and federal laws and regulations / or municipal; (ii) conflict with the rules of these Terms of Use, and (ii) violate the principles of morality and good attire. Any and all actions performed or content published by the User during the use of the Application shall be of its exclusive and integral responsibility, and shall exempt and indemnify AppBelchior from legal or extrajudicial claims, damages, losses and damages caused to AppBelchior, as a result of actions or manifestations. AppBelchior reserves the right to subscribe, delete or change items and content of the Application, and may temporarily suspend or cancel it, its sole discretion and any time, regardless of prior notice to the User. Likewise, AppBelchior may modify these Terms of Use, but the latest version is available for viewing on the Application itself. AppBelchior disclaims all liability for damages and losses of any nature that access, intercept, delete, modify, modify or manipulate, by unauthorized third parties, User data while using the application. As requested information to the User at the time of registration is to point to the user\'s use, please, be it judicial or of competent authority.</string>
    <string name="politica_de_privacidad_texto">All of your personal information collected will be used to help make your visit to our app as productive and enjoyable as possible. Ensuring the confidentiality of the personal data of our app users is important to AppBelchior.   All personal information relating to members, subscribers, customers or visitors using the AppBelchior application will be handled in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act of 26 October 1998 (Law No. 67/98). Personal information collected may include your name, email address, telephone number and / or mobile phone, date of birth and / or other. The use of the AppBelchior application assumes acceptance of this privacy agreement as well as the Terms of Use. AppBelchior staff reserves the right to change this agreement without prior notice. Therefore, we recommend that you review our privacy policy and terms of use on a regular basis so that you are always up-to-date.</string>
    <string name="btnEntrarGoogle">Sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="btnEntrarFacebook">Sign in with Facebook</string>
    <string name="btnEntrarEmail">Sign in with Email</string>
    <string name="btnCriarConta">Create an account</string>
    <string name="btnCadastrar">Sign up</string>
    <string name="ao_clicar_login_voce_concorda_com_os_nossos">" By signing in, you agree to our"</string>
    <string name="e">and our</string>
    <string name="termos_de_servico">terms of use</string>
    <string name="politica_de_privacidade">privacy policy</string>
    <string name="cancelar">Cancel</string>
    <string name="sucesso">Success</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="info">" Information"</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="yes">Ok</string>
    <string name="no">Cancel</string>
    <string name="warning">Alert</string>
    <string name="msg_cadastro_sucesso">Username registered successfully!</string>
    <string name="msg_erro_senha">Passwords are not match</string>
    <string name="msg_usuario_senha">username or password is invalid</string>
    <string name="msg_campos_email_senha">" Fill in the email and password fields!"</string>
    <string name="msg_falha_autenticacao">" Authentication failed"</string>
    <string name="msg_login_sucesso">" Login done successfully"</string>
    <string name="msg_erro_senha_minimo">" Enter a stronger password, at least 8 characters (letters and numbers)"</string>
    <string name="msg_erro_email_valido">Email typed is invalid. Enter a new Email</string>
    <string name="msg_erro_cadastro_existente">Email registered in the system!</string>
    <string name="nao_possui_login">No account yet?</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="entre_para_fazer_login">" Enter your details to sign in"</string>
    <string name="autentication">" Authentication"</string>
    <string name="politica_de_privacidade_texto">All of your personal information collected will be used to help make your visit to our app as productive and enjoyable as possible. Ensuring the confidentiality of the personal data of our app users is important to AppBelchior. All personal information relating to members, subscribers, customers or visitors using the AppBelchior application will be handled in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act of 26 October 1998 (Law No. 67/98). Personal information collected may include your name, email address, telephone number and / or mobile phone, date of birth and / or other. The use of the AppBelchior application assumes acceptance of this privacy agreement as well as the Terms of Use. AppBelchior staff reserves the right to change this agreement without prior notice. Therefore, we recommend that you review our privacy policy and terms of use on a regular basis so that you are always up-to-date.</string>
    <string name="cadastre_se">Sign up</string>
    <string name="edtEmail">E-mail</string>
    <string name="edtSenha">Password</string>
    <string name="edtConfSenha">confirm password</string>
    <string name="edtNome">Name</string>
    <string name="edtSobrenome">Last name</string>
    <string name="edtData">Birth</string>
    <string name="rdFeminino">" Female"</string>
    <string name="rdMasculino">Male</string>
    <string name="msg_erro_cadastro">Error while registering</string>
</resources>